in this tutorial I'll be demonstrating a
在本教程中，我将演示
simple technique for taking a single
一种简单的技巧，让你一次
object and filling it with another
对象，并用另一个
object using inkscape before we get
对象，然后使用Inkscape获取
started though if you want to learn more
如果您想了解更多信息，请开始学习
about how inkscape Works be sure to
关于Inkscape的工作原理，请务必
check out my inkscape master class it's
看看我的Inkscape大师课
a collection of over 80 videos where we
我们收集了80多个视频，其中我们
go over all of the tools and features in
查看中的所有工具和功能
inkscape and I explain what they are and
Inkscape和我解释了它们是什么
demonstrate how they work kind of like
演示它们是如何工作的
how I'll do in this video we even have a
我将如何在这个视频中我们甚至有一个
private Community where you can ask
私人社区，您可以在那里提问
questions and get help from me anytime
任何时候都可以向我提问并寻求帮助
you need it I'll have some information
你需要它，我会有一些信息的
about that down below if you want to
如果你想的话请看下面的内容
check that out and now that that out of
看看这个，现在看看这个
the way let's get started so I'm going
让我们开始吧，所以我要走了
to open up a blank document and I'm
打开一份空白文档，而我
going to grab my text tool by either
我要去拿我的文本工具
grabbing it from the toolbar over here
从这里的工具栏上抓取它
or just pressing the letter t on the
或者只是将字母t按在
keyboard and I'm going to click on the
键盘，我要点击
canvas and for this demonstration I'm
画布，在这个演示中我是
just going to use the letter s I'm going
我要用S这个字母，我要去
to use a large capital letter s I'm
要用大写字母S，我是
going to hold control and scale this up
将掌握控制权并扩大规模
so that we maintain the aspect ratio and
这样我们就可以保持纵横比，
let me open up my text editor by going
让我通过以下方式打开我的文本编辑器
to text and selecting text and font and
设置为文本并选择文本和字体
I'm going to change the font of this to
我要将这个的字体更改为
monserat Black and I'm going to use a
Monserat Black和我要用一个
very heavyweight front for this because
非常重量级的前线，因为
it gives us more space to fill in with
它给了我们更多的空间来填补
that object let me scale this up some
该对象使我可以将其放大一些
more I'm going to convert this to a path
更多的是，我将把它转换成一条路径
by going to path object to path and then
通过转到路径对象到路径，然后
I will quote unquote ungroup it by going
我将引用不引用，通过以下方式将其取消分组
to object ungroup now nothing visibly
反对现在拆分任何明显的东西
changes there but it just it's a
在那里发生了变化，但这只是一个
function that's required to make this
函数来实现这一点
work as needed and now I'm going to open
按需工作，现在我要打开
up the layers menu by going to layer and
通过转到层和层来向上打开层菜单
selecting layers and objects and if you
选择层和对象，如果您
notice here this text next object is
请注意，此处的文本下一个对象是
located on layer one I'm going to create
位于第一层，我将创建
a new layer on top of this where I'm
在这上面有一个新的层面，我在那里
going to place the object that I would
我要把我想要的东西
like to fill this in with so I'm going
想把这个填进去，所以我要走了
to click this plus icon up here and it's
点击这里的加号图标，它就是
going to add a new layer and I have an
要添加一个新层，我有一个
object already copied to my clipboard
对象已复制到我的剪贴板
I'm just going to press control V to
我只需按下Ctrl V键
paste that in there you can use any
把它粘贴在那里，你可以用任何
object you want to fill in your shape or
要填充到形状中的对象或
letter you can use a single object or as
字母您可以使用单个对象或作为
in my case I'm using a grouping of
在我的例子中，我使用了一组
objects here so I have this orange slice
物体在这里，所以我有这个橙色切片
that I created I'm just going to fill it
我所创造的，我只是要把它填满
in with this let me scale this down a
有了这个，让我把这个缩小到一个
little bit and I want to Center this I
有一点，我想把这个放在中间
want to put this in the top left corner
我想把这个放在左上角
of this object but first let me take
但首先让我来看看
this object and make note of the size if
此对象并记下大小，如果
I come up here to the the settings where
我来到这里的背景下，
it says W and H for width and height you
上面写着W和H代表你的宽度和高度
can see the size I'm going to size this
我能看到我要给这件衣服定号吗？
at 500 pixels wide and then it's going
500像素宽，然后它就会
to go to about 580 pixels high so I'm
到大约580像素高，所以我
going to make a mental note of this
我要在脑海中记下这一点
width and height for my instance here
此处我的实例的宽度和高度
I'm going to use 500 by 600 I'm just
我要用500乘以600，我只是
going to round up to make it easier I'm
我要去四舍五入，让它更容易
going to click on this object hold shift
要单击此对象，请按住Shift键
click on this object and I want to align
单击此对象，我想要对齐
those two together so let me come up
那两个人在一起，所以让我上来
here to object and go to align and
在这里反对，并转到对齐和
distribute and let me choose last
分发，让我最后选择
selected and I'm going to align the left
选中后，我将向左对齐
edges and the top edges so that it
边缘和顶端边缘，以便它
places the object in the top left corner
将对象放置在左上角
of this object's bounding box and now I
此对象的边界框，现在我
can click off of it to select every to
可在其上单击以选择每到
deselect everything so let me just come
取消所有选择，所以让我来吧
over here to my layers menu and make
在这里到我的层菜单，并使
sure I have everything as I need it this
当然，我什么都有，因为我需要它
object here is in Layer Two and this
这里的对象在第二层，这是
this object is layer one everything
这个对象是第一层的一切
looks good there now I'm going to use
看起来很好，现在我要用
the tiled clones feature to generate
要生成的平铺克隆功能
copies of this image inside or this
此图像的副本在里面或这个
graphic inside of this letter so to do
这封信里面的图形是这样做的
that I'm going to go to edit clone and
我要去编辑克隆和
choose create tiled clones and the
选择创建平铺克隆，然后选择
settings I'm going to use for this I'm
我将为此使用的设置我是
first going to come over here to scale
首先要到这里来规模化
and I want to make sure I have the
我想要确保我有
randomized column set to 50% for both
随机列均设置为50%
the X and the Y AIS make sure you have
X和Y AIS确保您拥有
zeros in here it should be by default
此处为零，默认情况下应为
but if not just make sure to enter zeros
但如果不是这样，请确保输入零
and then I'll come over here to the
然后我会到这里来
rotation we want to rotate this object
旋转我们想要旋转此对象
as well we don't want it to just be the
同样，我们不希望它仅仅是
same rotation all the way through we
在整个过程中都是一样的旋转
want randomized rotation so I set the
想要随机旋转，所以我设置了
randomize to 100% I'm going to leave
随机到100%我要走了
these two at zero and bluring opacity
这两个是零和模糊的不透明
I'll leave that empty color I'll leave
我会留下那空虚的颜色，我会留下
that empty and I'll come over here to
那是空的，我会过来这里
trace you want to enable this option
跟踪您要启用此选项
right here that says trace the drawing
就在这里，上面写着追踪图纸
under the Clone SL spray items and we're
在克隆SL喷雾项目下，我们
going to choose the opacity setting and
选择不透明度设置，然后
then only the presence setting make sure
那么只有在线状态设置才能确保
you deselect these other settings here
您可以在此处取消选择这些其他设置
and now when we choose between rows and
现在，当我们在行和行之间进行选择时
columns or width and height we're going
列或宽度和高度，我们要
to choose width and height and we're
选择宽度和高度，我们正在
going to enter that width and height of
要输入的宽度和高度
this object that you made note of
你注意到的这个物体
earlier so for my example here I was
早些时候，对于我的例子，我是
doing this earlier so these numbers are
早些时候这样做，所以这些数字是
already there it's 500 by 600 so now
已经有500乘600了，所以现在
with that in place I'm going to click
准备就绪后，我将单击
the create button and it should generate
按钮，它应该会生成
copies of that object within the other
该对象在另一对象中的副本
object now if you notice the copies are
如果您注意到这些副本是
kind of large I didn't really like how
有点大，我真的不喜欢
that came out so I'm going to press
它出来了，所以我要按下
press command Z or control Z to undo
按命令Z或Ctrl Z撤消
that and I'm going to make this object a
我要把这个物体变成一个
little smaller and try that again I'm
小一点，再试一次，我是
going to make that a little bit smaller
会让它变得更小一点
let me Zoom back out and click the
让我缩小，然后单击
create button again and see how that
再次创建按钮，并查看如何
goes okay that looks a little better but
挺好的，看起来好一点，但是
still a little large let me undo that
还是有点大，让我把它解开。
again and I'll make this a little bit
再来一次，我会把这个做得有点
smaller and this should do the trick
再小一点，这个应该行得通。
this time let me try it one more
这一次让我再试一次
time okay that looks a lot better so now
时间没问题，看起来好多了，所以现在
that that's in place let me zoom in on
已经就位了，让我放大看
this a little bit let me close out of
这一点让我接近了
the tille Clones menu we don't need that
磁贴克隆菜单，我们不需要它
anymore if you notice the objects are
如果你注意到这些物体
overlapping each other which doesn't
相互重叠，而不是
really create a good effect we want them
真的创造出我们想要的良好效果
to be not overlapping so to correct that
不能重叠，所以要纠正
I'm going to hold control and shift and
我要按住控制和变速键
take this original object and scale it
取此原始对象并对其进行缩放
down a little bit and if you notice when
往下一点，如果你注意到什么时候
I do that all of the other objects scale
我做的就是所有其他物体都成比例
down as well because these are all
也要下来，因为这些都是
linked clones so whatever I do to this
链接的克隆，所以无论我对此做什么
original object it will also happen to
原始对象也会发生这种情况
these other objects so scaling it up and
这些其他物体将其放大
down will help increase and decrease the
向下将有助于增加和减少
density of the objects within the shape
形状内对象的密度
and that right there looks like a good
就在那里看起来像是一个很好的
happy medium I'm going to move this out
好的，我要把这个搬出去
of the way if you notice we have some
当然，如果你注意到我们有一些
imperfections in here a lot of these
在这里有很多不完美的地方
objects went outside of the shape that's
对象超出了形状，即
okay we could just go through and click
好的，我们可以直接通过点击
on them and press delete one by one to
并逐个按Delete键以
get rid of them so I'm just going to go
把它们处理掉，所以我要走了
through here and delete these real
通过这里并删除这些真实的
quick and another thing you'll probably
还有一件事，你很可能会
want to do let me just get rid of that
想做什么，让我把它处理掉
one as well another thing you'll want to
一件事和另一件事一样，你会想
do is go and move these around a little
我要做的就是把这些东西搬来搬去
bit just to correct the spacing and we
比特只是为了纠正间距，我们
we're just going to do this manually
我们将手动执行此操作
we're going to go through these one by
我们将通过以下几个步骤来了解这些问题
one let me come up here to the top of
一位让我登上这座城市的顶端
the layers menu I'm going to collapse
我要折叠的层菜单
layer two so I can see layer one and I
第二层，所以我可以看到第一层和我
want to lock layer one so that I don't
我想锁定第一层，这样我就不会
accidentally move the layer or the
意外移动层或
object in the layer with what I'm about
对象在与我有关的层中
to do because what what I'm going to do
因为我要做的是
now is I'm just going to manually move
现在我只需要手动移动
these objects around so that they are
这些物体周围，所以他们是
sitting on the edge of the shape or the
坐在形状的边缘或
letter and you may have to just manually
信件，您可能只需手动
adjust these so that they
调整这些，以使它们
are uh evenly spaced out and they don't
是均匀分布的，它们不会
overlap each other or they don't look
相互重叠，否则他们看不到
like they're big gaps between them so
就像他们之间有很大的差距一样
I'm just going to balance these out a
我只是要把这些平衡一下
little bit and again this is something
一点一点，再一次，这是一些东西
we're going to do manually you can hold
我们将手动操作，您可以拿着
control and scale it up and down and if
控制并放大和缩小它，如果
you want to make additional copies you
你想再复印几份吗？
could just click and drag it and then
只需点击并拖动它，然后
press the space bar and it'll make
按空格键，它就会变成
copies of it so you can just make copies
复制它，这样你就可以复制它
in there like that by pressing your
像这样按下你的按键
space bar and I'll move these around a
空格键和我将这些移动到一个
little bit as well and I think you get
也有一点，我想你会得到
the idea so let me just go through here
我的想法是让我先在这里说一遍
real quick and just straighten this out
非常迅速地把这件事弄清楚
so that it looks good and then I will
好让它看起来不错，然后我就会
catch up with you when I'm finished
等我做完了再跟你说
all right so for the most part I
好吧，所以在很大程度上我
finished up here there's a few loose
在这里结束了，有一些松动
ends that need to be tied up this one
需要绑好的这一端
looks a little big and there's some
看起来有点大，还有一些
empty gaps in there but you should get
那里空荡荡的，但你应该
the idea by now the really important
到目前为止，真正重要的想法是
thing when doing this is to make sure
这样做时要做的是确保
that you have these objects as close to
你把这些物体放在最接近的地方
the edge of the larger object as
较大对象的边缘作为
possible because that's what's really
有可能，因为这才是真正的
going to help it maintain its appearance
去帮助它保持它的外表
as the original shape if they get too
作为原始形状，如果它们太
far from The Edge it's going to kind of
远离边缘，它将会有点
lose its appearance so that's really
失去了它的外观，所以这真的是
important and once you're done doing all
重要的是，一旦你完成了所有
of this these objects should still be
其中，这些对象应该仍然是
linked together so you can still
链接在一起，因此您仍然可以
increase or decrease the size of these
增加或减小这些文件的大小
clones if you want to using the original
克隆(如果您想使用原始的
but I think it looks good as it was so
但我认为它看起来很好
I'll just put that back and now that
我只是把它放回去，现在
that's done let me come back up here to
做完了，让我回到这里来
my top the top of my layers menu I'm
我的顶层在我层菜单的顶端我是
going to collapse Layer Two where all
要坍塌第二层，所有的
those all of those clones are and I'll
所有这些克隆人都是，我会
come over here to layer one and I'm just
到这里来做第一层，我只是
going to turn off the visibility of it
我要关闭它的可见性
and you can see the effect now I've
你现在可以看到我的效果了
taken this object and filled in the
获取此对象并填充
other object with copies of it and maybe
其他对象和它的副本，可能
I'll even make this a little
我甚至会让它变得有点
bigger yeah that looks pretty good I
更大的，是的，看起来很不错
like how that looks right there and yeah
就像它看起来那样，是的。
I think that should do it for this
我想这就够了。
tutorial so that's how you can use the
教程，这就是您如何使用
tiled clones feature in inkscape to fill
Inkscape中的平铺克隆功能以填充
in an object with another object if you
在一个对象和另一个对象中，如果您
have any questions just leave a comment
如有任何疑问，请留言
below and as always thanks for watching
下面并一如既往地感谢您的收看
if you found this lesson useful then
如果你觉得这一课很有用，那么
consider checking out my inkscape master
考虑一下我的Inkscape大师
class it's a collection of over 60
班级它是一个超过60个人的集合
videos where I go over all of the tools
我浏览了所有工具的视频
and features in inkscape and I explain
和Inkscape中的功能，我解释
what they are and demonstrate how they
它们是什么并演示它们如何
work kind of like how I did in this
就像我在这件事上做的那样
video we even have a private Community
视频我们甚至有一个私人社区
where you can ask questions and get help
在这里您可以提出问题并获得帮助
for me anytime you want and best of all
对我来说，你想要的任何时候，最好的是
there's no monthly membership fees you
你不需要缴纳月费
just pay $17 one time and you're in for
只需一次性支付17美元，你就会面临
Life I'll have some information about
我会有一些关于生活的信息
that down below if you want to check
如果您想查看下面的内容
that out as always thanks for watching
这是一如既往的感谢收看
[Music]
[音乐]
oh
噢